const dayFiveQuestions = [
  {
    question: "How many Medina Surahs (Medina Chapter) do we have?",
    options: ["28", "29", "30", "31", "32"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the companion whose real name was mentioned in the Quran?",
    options: [
      "Muhammad bn ‘Abdillah",
      "Abubakr Siddiq",
      "Umar bn Khatab",
      "Zaydu bn Harithah",
      "‘Abdullah bn ‘Abbas",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the first word of Allaah that was first revealed to Prophet Muhammad (peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) by Angel JIbril (May the peace be upon him)?",
    options: [
      "Alif Lam Mim",
      "Bimilah",
      "Iqrah",
      "A’undhubillah",
      "Alhamdulillah",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How many times was the name Muhammad mentioned in the Quran?",
    options: [
      "one time",
      "two times",
      "three times",
      "four times",
      "five times",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which word falls at the middle of Quran?",
    options: [
      "Walyatalatof",
      "yasaluunaka",
      "fajama’naaum",
      "Fa asqaynakumuuh",
      "Fasayakfiikahumu",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which verse of the Quran do we find the name “Allah” two times sequentially without an alphabet separating them?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Baqarah",
      "Suratul Al-Imran",
      "Suratun Nisaa",
      "Suratul Maidah",
      "Suratul An’am",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Al Quran script diacritics (phonetic guide marks; vowel marks) began during the tenure of …….",
    options: [
      "Abubakr Sidiq",
      "Umar bn Khattab",
      "‘Uthman bn ‘Affan",
      "Ali bn Abi Talib",
      "Khaleefah ‘Abdul Maliki bn Mirwan.",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which Chapter of the Quran can we find the name Allah in each verse of it?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Ikhlas",
      "Suratul Mujadalah",
      "Suratul Jumu’at",
      "Suratul Hashr",
      "Suratus Saf",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "How many Mekkah Surahs do we have?",
    options: ["28", "86", "63", "43", "32"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "How many Chapters of the Quran start with ‘Alhamdulillah’?",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5"],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "How many Hizb (division) are there in the Quran?",
    options: ["6666", "313", "114", "60", "30"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many Sajdah (prostration of recitation) are there in the Quran?",
    options: ["10", "15", "20", "25", "30"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "How many Chapters of the Quran start with Alif Laam Meem?",
    options: ["6", "5", "4", "3", "2"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "They began putting dots on alphabets of the Quran during the tenure of ……………",
    options: [
      "Abubakr Sidiq",
      "Umar bn Khattab",
      "‘Uthman bn ‘Affan",
      "Ali bn Abi Talib",
      "Khaleefah ‘Abdul Maliki bn Mirwan.",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Chapter of the Quran comprises of two Bismillah Rahmani Raheem?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Ankabut",
      "Suratul Insan",
      "Suratun Naml",
      "Suratul Rahman",
      "Suratul Mulk",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
];
export default dayFiveQuestions;
